All the battles fought
Take the armor off
Hold me in your gentle heart
My head simmers down
When you come around
Clear the poison from my thoughts
Till the fall of the human race
And the lights flicker out in space
I would stay, I would stay right where you are
When all of Heaven's angels are dead
If this is all that's left
Two of us for life
It was always you and I
When even time has come to its end
When it's flipped on its head
Two of us for life
It was always you, it was always you and I
Found my missing piece
Oxygen I breathe
You're the fire in my soul
Right from the first sight
Till the afterlife
Finally, I've come home
Till the fall of the human race
And the lights flicker out in space
I would stay, I would stay right where you are
When all of Heaven's angels are dead
If this is all that's left
Two of us for life
It was always you and I
When even time has come to its end
When it's flipped on its head
Two of us for life
It was always you, it was always you and I
Even when all else is lost
I would stay right where you are
When all of Heaven's angels are dead
If this is all that's left
Two of us for life
It was always you and I
When all of Heaven's angels are dead
If this is all that's left
Two of us for life
It was always you and I
When even time has come to its end
When it's flipped on its head
Two of us for life
It was always you, it was always you and I